componentart.com 2014-06-26

# ComponentArt - Privacy Notice

At Datazen Software the privacy and security of our customers and users are of paramount importance. We understand your concern over the privacy of any personal information you supply to us, and your need to control this information.

**Windows Store - ComponentArt Dev Tools App Privacy Policy**

_Information Collected_ \- The "ComponentArt Dev Tools" application does not collect any personal information. You may use this application without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. 

_External Links_ \- The "ComponentArt Dev Tools" application does not include links to any third party sites or services. 

**ComponentArt Website - Anonymous Use**

Our overall policy is one of collecting only the information necessary to communicate with our customers about the Datazen Software products they are interested in, and/or the information required to process the sale of one of our products. We do not collect any other information, nor share any of the information we collect with anyone.

You are free to visit our website, and access any information contained therein without revealing any information about yourself. Any identifying information collected in our web traffic logs is standard anonymous, domain-based information only — and may also include information such as your browser type, the referring site/URL, the time and duration of your visit, and the pages accessed. At no time will you be personally identifiable by us, and all web server log information is used for anonymous, aggregated traffic and site activity analysis.

**ComponentArt Website - Personal Information Collected During the Download of Trial Software**

When you download one of our products for evaluation, we ask for a limited amount of personal information that will allow us to identify you in order to communicate with you effectively about the products you are interested in.

Currently, when you create your user account we collect your username, e-mail address, company name, your general type of job function, the size of your development team, and the products you are interested in evaluating. In addition, our download logs automatically collect information such as your browser type, the date and time of your visit, the referring site/URL, and your IP address.

During the download process, we also provide the option for you to allow us to contact you in the future regarding the product you are accessing (including updates, fixes, enhancements and other information), and other Datazen Software products that you may be interested in. We will not communicate with you if you choose not to enable this option — and we provide a mechanism for you to opt out of this communication in the future, if you so desire.

At no time will your personal information be sold, rented, or revealed in any way to a 3rd party. We will not use the information you provide to us for any purpose other than to communicate with you about our products in the most efficient way possible.

**ComponentArt Website - Personal Information Collected During the Purchase of Our Products**

When you purchase one of our products, we ask for the standard and necessary information required to identify you and process the transaction. This includes information about you, and information about the product you are purchasing.

At present, the information collected during the purchase process includes your full name, address, telephone number, company name, e-mail address, IP address, the purchase date and time, and sufficient credit card information (type, number, expiry date) to authorize the transaction with your card provider.

When you purchase one of our products, we automatically add your name and e-mail address to our database of customers in order to communicate with you in the future about the product you have purchased (including updates, fixes, enhancements and other information), and other Datazen Software products that you may be interested in. We will not communicate with you if you choose to disable this option — and we provide a mechanism for you to opt out of this communication in the future, if you so desire.

At no time will your personal information nor purchase information (including credit card information) be sold, rented, or revealed in any way to a 3rd party. We will not use the information you provide to us for any purpose other than to communicate with you about our products in the most efficient way possible.

**ComponentArt Website - The Security of Our Technology**

Datazen Software makes every reasonable effort to ensure the absolute security of all of the systems that comprise our website, database, and e-commerce mechanisms — as well as the workstations that access these systems for administration and analysis.

We take all steps necessary to ensure that our own systems, as well as the systems of our service providers are physically secure, and electronically secure. All company systems and affiliated systems are password-protected. Any and all transmissions of sensitive information (such as customer credit card information) — from customer workstations to web and e-commerce servers, between and among processing and storage systems, and from company systems to administration workstations — are fully encrypted.

We do not utilize bulk mailing technology that reveals your e-mail address to others being mailed to (for instance, during the bulk mailing of a newsletter).

At no time will any Datazen Software software product collect nor reveal any personal information about anyone using the product — during development or production use within an application — unless the Datazen Software product or source code has been specifically modified or configured for this purpose by the customer.

**ComponentArt Website - Definition of "Third Party"**

For the sake of clarity, a "third party" is defined as anyone not a part of, nor directly affiliated with Datazen Software Inc. Those directly affiliated include service providers (who, in providing services such the hosting and processing mechanisms of our websites have access to the information contained within their own systems) and resellers and affiliate sale partners (who collect customer and transaction information on our behalf).

In no case will anyone directly affiliated with Datazen Software Inc. use the information revealed to them for any purpose other than to provide the information to Datazen Software for the use outlined in the preceding sections above.

**For Further Information**

If you have any further questions regarding the information Datazen Software collects, or how we use it, then please feel free to contact us by e-mail at: [info@datazen.com](mailto:info@datazen.com "info@datazen.com"), or in writing at:

Datazen Software Inc.  
511 King Street West, Suite 400  
Toronto, Ontario  
M5V 1K4  
Canada
